kgbpeople.com 2015-05-02

# Privacy Policy - www.kgbpeople.com

### Privacy policy

The website located at kgbpeople.com ("the Site") is operated by Centroid Media B.V. ("we", "us" or "our"). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you ("User" or "you" or "your"), what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal data through the Site. The Site is operated in and controlled from The Netherlands and we are legally obliged to use your Personal Information (as defined hereinafter) in line with the laws concerning the protection of Personal Information. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Site, or if you wish to unsubscribe from any of the people search and/or reputation management services that we provide via the Site ("the Service") for which you have previously registered, please contact us at [info@kgbpeople.com](mailto:info@kgbpeople.com) or at the address at the end of this policy.

**We encourage you to read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing and/or using the site, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please exit this page and do not access or use the site.**

#### Types of Information We Collect

  * ##### Personal Information.

If you register on the Site, we ask for and record some Personal Information. "Personal Information" means information you knowingly choose to disclose to us, such as your name, email address, account password, which information contains details about your identity. We may use your email address to send you updates and news about the Site.

You may decline to submit your Personal Information to the Site, although this may affect our ability to provide certain functions of the Service to you.

  * ##### Contributions

We store and may publicly display your Contributions to the Site in order to provide and enhance the Service that we offer. When we display your Contributions, we may do so together with your User name. "Contributions" refers to any content you submit or post to the Site for public display, such as links to content on third party websites, ratings, comments, photos, facts, and other similar types of information. Please do not include information in your Contributions that you expect to be kept private or that may infringe the rights of any third party.

  * ##### Feedback

If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any Personal Information and other content you provide in your communication so we can effectively respond to your communication.

  * ##### Activity

We automatically record information relating to your use of the Site (through the use of electronic tools such as cookies, web beacons or pixel tags), such as the searches you undertake, the pages you visit, your browser or phone type, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, requested Uniform Resource Locator ("URL"), referring URL, and timestamp information, and other similar types of information. We use this information to operate and administer the Site and to provide the highest possible level of service to you.

  * ##### Cookies and Other Navigational Tools

To enhance your experience with the Site, we store cookies on your computer and we may use web beacons or pixel tags. Pixel tags and web beacons are graphic images placed on certain pages on our Site or in our emails to you that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies also allow us to collect non-personal information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other Personal Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering on the Site. However, once you choose to furnish the Site with Personal Information, this Personal Information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at the Site (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to the Site), and to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. In addition, we may use third party advertising companies to display advertisements on the Site. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.

#### How We Use Your Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself, including any Personal Information, to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our Service, and to offer you other products, programs, or services we believe may be of interest to you.

We may use or disclose your Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

If we believe it is necessary, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (ii) investigate, enforce or apply our Site Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy; (iii) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, or property or that of our Users, affiliates, the public or other third parties. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena, or other similar governmental request we may receive.

We may aggregate data and disclose such data only in aggregate and in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for marketing and promotional purposes (e.g. to perform statistical analyses of User behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site). Aggregated information does not identify any User individually.

We use information about which links have been followed and whether action has been taken on another party's website to improve our offerings and to customize the Service we provide to you via the Site.

Technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, IP address, pages visited, and average time spent on the Site, may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our website design and functionality.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you choose to use the separate products or services offered by such third-party advertising companies, disclose information to the providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their products or services.

#### Release of Your Information to Third Parties

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we generally do not sell, trade, rent or share Personal Information that we collect with third parties unless we have your consent to do so.

We may transfer your information to a third party in connection with a sale or acquisition of our business or substantially all of its assets (or a merger of our business with another company). If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personal Information. However, Personal Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### Security of Your Personal Information

While this Privacy Policy expresses our standards for maintenance of Personal Information, we are not in a position to guarantee the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in unintentional disclosure of Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Updating and Correcting Your Personal Information

We encourage you to promptly update or correct your Personal Information if it changes. We ask individual Users to identify themselves and the information requested to be updated or corrected before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required.

You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed, in which case we will also ask you to identify yourself. However, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Site. In addition, it may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information, even if you terminate your account or unsubscribe from the Site, because we periodically backup information.

Please note also that your information may still be available on the website that we originally indexed the results from. You should contact the source or work with the original site to remove any other information pertaining to you.

#### How to Reach Us

If you wish to contact us on matters related to this Privacy Policy, or any other matter related to the Service (including customer service inquiries), you can reach us using the contact details set forth below:

Centroid Media b.v.  
Burgemeester Reigerstraat 78  
3581KW Utrecht  
The Netherlands  
Telephone: +31(0)50 7110329  
Email: [info@kgbpeople.com](mailto:info@kgbpeople.com)

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. You may review updates to our Privacy Policy at any time via links on the Site. You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of an annual or revised Privacy Policy on the Site and that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, and/or by means of a notice on our home page. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Site. It is your responsibility to review the Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service and/or the Site after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

#### Sole Statement

The foregoing statements, terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy represent the sole statement of our Privacy Policy, and no summary or other statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on August 18, 2010 and is effective immediately.
